[
  {
    "question": "What's the name of the boss you need to kill in Dragon Slayer I?",
    "answer": "Elvarg"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where do you obtain a raw pheasant?",
    "answer": "Freaky forester random event"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name one the rewards you get from the Drill Demon random event?",
    "answer": "Camo top"
  },
  {
    "question": "Whats the name of the first player who completed the Inferno?",
    "answer": "Woox"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name one of the main developers for RuneBot?",
    "answer": "Chaflie"
  },
  {
    "question": "What cooking level do you need to cook Raw manta ray?",
    "answer": "91"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much experience does Willow logs grant (woodcutting)?",
    "answer": "67.5"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much cooking xp do you get for cooking a lobster?",
    "answer": "120"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the bow weapon dropped from Raids I?",
    "answer": "Twisted bow"
  },
  {
    "question": "Mention any race of monster that follows the God of War / General Graardor.",
    "answer": "Goblin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blank: R_neBot",
    "answer": "RuneBot"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much does Void knight gloves cost at the Pest control reward shop?",
    "answer": "150"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which cape is the most powerful melee cape?",
    "answer": "Infernal cape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name a guthix shield.",
    "answer": "Guthix kiteshield"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of this monster?",
    "answer": "molanisk"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the ranged level required to enter the Ranging guild?",
    "answer": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of pages are used to create a book of war?",
    "answer": "Bandos"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where are Grizzly bears typically found?",
    "answer": "Forests"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was pest control released?",
    "answer": "2006"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which monster drops the Tzhaar-ket-om?",
    "answer": "Tzhaar-ket"
  },
  {
    "question": "What city in RuneScape does Horacio live?",
    "answer": "Lumbridge"
  },
  {
    "question": "Name a location where you can fish using a big fishing net?",
    "answer": "Catherby"
  },
  {
    "question": "What's the combat level of Jad/TzTok-Jad?",
    "answer": "702"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shield is used to protect against dragonfire?",
    "answer": "Dfs"
  },
  {
    "question": "What prayer level do you need to use protect from mage?",
    "answer": "37"
  },
  {
    "question": "Fill in the blanks... Ir_n_an _tw",
    "answer": "Ironman btw"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who do you speak to in order to start the Animal Magnetism quest?",
    "answer": "Ava"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the island where Elvarg is located?",
    "answer": "Crandor"
  },
  {
    "question": "RuneScape was created in a basement by Andrew g_w_r and his brothers... Fill in the blanks!",
    "answer": "Gower"
  },
  {
    "question": "How much does the entire Void knight equipment set cost at the Pest control reward shop? (top, robe, gloves, helm)",
    "answer": "850"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where can Yenrab be found?",
    "answer": "Slepe"
  },
  {
    "question": "On which island is Giant mosquito's found?",
    "answer": "Mos Le'Harmless"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many quest points do you need before you can do Dragon Slayer I?",
    "answer": "32"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which quest are you rewarded the Silly jester costume from?",
    "answer": "the fremennik isles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Dessous's combat level?",
    "answer": "139"
  }
]